[theme music playing]
[Raul] What if Arnaldo
really has a problem?
How dare you say that to your own son?
Someone is laughing,
and I have to stop it.
No!
[Ivy] If you could only see Arnaldo.
All my plans are about to unfold.
Whatever happened to Arnaldo,
I know you were behind it.
-Be careful.
-I am being cautious.
Slowly but surely, my plans are unfolding.
But this isn't the end of it.
What more will you do?
[man] Twenty million pesos, Mayor.
Bring it to the plaza within one hour.
If you don't, Ivy Aguas will die.
Ivy!
I will not be threatened by nobody.
[screams]
The Ardientes are desperate
to work with you.
But Diego's group keeps pushing you away.
I don't have to worry about that.
That Madrigal. We need him in our group.
You should work on that. Understood?
[goon] Congressman, confirmed.
Jaguar has been watching Diego's camp.
Do you mean to tell me that Jaguar
and that snot-nosed Diego are teaming up?
What are you waiting for?
Bring me that man!
[Rufo] Why did you bring me here?
To break Jaguar's trust.
Try to destroy his will.
Congressman, you're
talking to the wrong man.
Rufo, what is it going to be?
[Arnaldo] Clara, prepare 20 million pesos.
[grunts]
-Good afternoon.
-[crowd chants] Diego Torillo!
How are you?
-[supporters continue chanting]
-Good afternoon.
[Anna] Don't forget to vote for Diego…
-this coming election.
-Hello.
Thank you. Thank you.
Hello, everyone!
-[Anna] This election…
-How are you, everyone?
[Anna] Please don't forget.
-How are you?
-[supporters continue chanting]
Let's take a selfie.
[supporters continue chanting]
-Thank you.
-Hello, how are you?
Can I hug you?
[supporters continue chanting]
[Emilia] Okay. Where is everybody?
Where are Arnaldo and Ivy?
They haven't been
answering my calls, ma'am.
What?! Arnaldo can't be absent
from his own campaign!
-[supporters] Diego Torillo!
-Hello. How are you?
[supporters chanting] Vote for change!
How are you?
Hi, sir. How are you doing?
[supporters chanting] Vote for Diego!
[Anna] Don't forget to vote for Diego!
-Vote for change!
-Thank you.
[supporters] Vote for Diego!
Vote for change!
We can't fall behind schedule.
-I know!
-Honestly, just cancel it.
Emilia and I can't go there alone.
You know, Auntie, you have a point.
-Cancel it.
-Yes, ma'am.
But, we're still pushing
through with our errand.
[tense music playing]
[ominous music playing]
[gasps]
[groans]
[grunts]
[exhales]
Ivy?
Ivy!
Hey!
Whoever you are, show yourself!
[man] Give me my money first!
[ominous music playing]
Show me Ivy first!
[man laughs]
[man] You never stopped
being arrogant, did you?
[scoffs]
You, the Prince of the Ardientes.
But where's your grandfather now?
How about your money?
How about your power? Your weapons?
They're gone!
The only ones here right now…
are me and you!
And today is the day you will fall.
[tense music playing]
[laughs]
[laughs maniacally]
Oh, please.
Where are you?
Why don't you come out and show your face?
Oh, I know.
You're just being chicken.
Have it your way.
Chicken!
[laughs]
[suspenseful music playing]
Hey, Mayor.
[dramatic music]
What's up?
[tense music playing]
[screams]
[chanting] Diego Torillo!
Vote for change now!
-[unsettling music playing]
-[supporters continue chanting]
[chanting] Diego Torillo!
Vote for change now!
[supporters continue chanting]
[Diego] Ivy, why aren't you
here at the campaign?
Arnaldo isn't here, either.
Is something wrong?
[tense music playing]
Where are they?
Diego, is something wrong?
Where's Ivy?
It's nothing. Let's go.
[tense music playing]
Mr. Torillo, I'm glad you made it.
Where are the Ardientes?
Mayor Arnaldo's camp canceled,
but you can proceed with your campaign.
All right?
-Excuse me.
-Thank you.
[Marlon] Batch, I think the
Ardientes are up to something.
This isn't good.
[tense music playing]
-Good morning.
-Good morning, ma'am.
It'll get even better
so proceed as planned.
Yes, ma'am.
[ominous music playing]
DIEGO FOR THE NEW ARDIENTE
[Diego] Hello, everyone!
Thank you for coming here today.
I want to introduce myself to you.
I am Diego Torillo.
I am running for governor of this town.
[cheering and applause]
We will be giving away a few supplies.
-[supporters chanting]
-I hope it helps.
Line up over here, please.
This is for you.
[supporters chanting] Diego Torillo!
[chuckles]
-[supporters chanting]
-Thank you.
Diego Torillo for real change!
[Anna] Diego!
-[supporters continue chanting]
-[ominous music playing]
Over here.
[Claire] Emilia, stop this already.
You're violating your peace agreement
with Diego's camp.
Auntie, this is an unelaborate carnage.
This won't hurt so bad.
[supporters] Diego Torillo!
Just stand here and wait in line.
There's enough for everyone.
Come with me
if you don't want to get hurt.
Don't scream.
[supporters] Diego Torillo
for real change!
-Come on.
-Diego Torillo!
[Claire] Goodness, Emilia.
What will you get out of this?
Well, Auntie, I want
to show Miss Lily Cruz
that I can embarrass her
the same way she embarrassed me.
But she'll get a lot worse.
I'll make sure of that.
[ominous music playing]
-[supporters chanting]
-Let go of me!
[chuckles]
This is just so exciting, Auntie.
Diego Torillo for a new Ardiente!
[chanting] Diego Torillo…
Batch, it's Lily!
It's Lily!
Move!
Lily!
-[Lily grunts]
-Come here!
-Hurry up!
-Hey!
Hey!
Where are you taking me?!
-Come on!
-Let me go!
[tense music playing]
Are you going to kill us?!
Danny, give me that!
-[screaming]
-[grunts]
Shoot!
Diego!
Diego, be careful!
Who sent you?!
-Answer me!
-[whistles]
There!
Get him out of here.
What are you waiting for?!
This isn't a movie!
Drive! Let's go!
[tense music playing]
Mr. Diego, that's enough.
[Marlon] Diego!
-[Anna] Diego, it's over.
-[Marlon] Let them do their job!
[indistinct chatter]
Are you okay, Batch?
-Lily, are you hurt?!
-Are you okay?
-How about you?
-I'm fine.
-Thank you, Diego.
-They're okay. Thanks.
[indistinct chatter]
[woman] Arrest him!
I'm sure the Ardientes are behind this.
[tense music playing]
[ominous music playing]
How have you been, Mayor?
[laughs]
It's been a while!
How are things, Mayor?
You know what?
I want to applaud you
for your grand entrance,
but I'm all tied up.
How's business doing?
Business is doing well.
But, seriously, what are you high on?
You think you'll get away with this?
A lunatic like you won't.
You were the psycho
in the town square, right?
Psycho.
That's right.
[laughs]
Where's Ivy?
-Where is she?!
-That she-devil?
She's on her way to hell!
You're all the same…
You may have money,
but you're all just evil!
You're all bad people,
and you're going to hell!
[ominous music playing]
You want money, right? Twenty million?
You won't get your money until I get Ivy.
Where is she?!
[grunts]
That's not going to happen!
Give me my money,
and I'll tell you where she is.
[scoffs]
But if you don't…
[labored breathing]
You won't find her alive,
and she's going straight to hell!
You can all burn down there together!
[scoffs]
Oh, right!
She wanted me to give you this.
Here.
You bastard!
Where is she?!
Let me see her! What did you do to her?!
I'm going to kill you!
I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
-Let her go!
-Wait!
[laughs]
-You bastard!
-You should see yourself!
[grunts]
I'm going to kill you!
Who's the psycho now?
[labored breathing]
[laughing]
If you just brought the money with you,
we wouldn't have a problem now.
I'm actually surprised, Mayor.
Aren't you generous?
Because your family is the
richest and greediest of all!
Mayor.
Twenty million?
[scoffs]
That's nothing, right?
There's one thing I'm curious about.
Why are you after the money now?
-Weren't you an activist?
-[sighs]
You even testified against my family.
Am I right? Answer me.
[sighs]
Yes.
But what happened to the other witnesses?
What happened to them?
Of course, I had them killed!
I even killed the others myself.
[laughs]
[laughs maniacally]
This only proves…
there's no place for justice in Ardiente!
What do we have instead?
Violence.
Bloodshed.
And wealth!
That's all!
And that's what I'm going
to take from you!
[tense music playing]
Thank goodness you're safe
despite what Emilia did to you.
Yes, Auntie Camia.
Good thing Diego was there.
My goodness.
I suddenly got worried about Lily.
I've been texting her,
but she hasn't replied yet.
Maybe she just went
somewhere with Arnaldo.
They might be busy
preparing for their wedding.
But I feel that something's wrong.
I'm a mother so I can sense it
if my daughter is in danger.
Don't worry too much.
Ivy can take care of herself.
I'm sure she knows what she's doing.
I just want to make sure
she's safe all the time.
I want to know what she's up to.
We all do.
[somber music playing]
So, Mayor…
Where's my 20 million pesos?!
Mayor!
[sighs] Where is it?!
Can we please stop prolonging this?!
Where is it? Where is it?!
Where is Ivy?!
I want to see her.
What if you don't?!
You won't have your money!
Then you won't ever see Ivy again.
[both chuckle]
Do you think that I believe
anything you say?!
You don't have Ivy!
Everything you said was a lie!
Ivy isn't here!
She's not here!
Oh, a gun!
Do you think you can scare me with that?
Ivy's not here!
If she was here,
you would've shown her to me!
But no!
No money, no Ivy!
Nothing!
[whispers] Nothing! Nothing. Nothing.
[heavy breathing]
-Nothing?
-Nothing.
[line rings]
Hello!
Put Ivy Aguas on the phone.
Now!
[unsettling music playing]
[Arthur exhales sharply]
Hello!
[laughs]
Ivy!
So…
You're still alive there, huh?
Someone wants to talk to you.
Should I put him on the line?
Answer me, Miss Aguas!
-[laughs] No one's on the line.
-There…
[laughs]
[ominous music playing]
Ivy?
[muffled screaming] Hon! Hon!
Ivy!
-Hon!
-What did they do-- Ivy!
You bastard! Let her go!
I'll give you everything.
I'll give you everything, just let her go.
[muffled screaming]
[sobbing] Hon!
Hon! [whimpers]
[phone clatters]
The Ardientes are all devious!
[laughs]
-Wait--
-How can I be sure…
that you'll give me everything I want?
I can even buy your soul, you idiot.
But you know what else I can do?
[suspenseful music playing]
[grunts]
[groans]
What now?!
Stand up! Come here!
[grunts]
[tense music playing]
What now, Arthur?
I always get what I want!
So give me back my fiancée
before I blow your brains out.
[grunts]
Go ahead!
[laughs]
What now, huh?
You Ardientes really are something else.
You all think you're so high and mighty.
So, Mayor…
Take it from me.
I think Carlotta and Nimfa are
calling you to the other side.
They might even pay you a visit.
Each and every one of you!
Are you messing with me?
Mayor…
You're messing--
Think twice about everything
you're going to do.
You don't want to marry
a corpse now, do you?
[tense music playing]
My goodness, Emilia.
You're being reckless again.
Can you please just be still
and go with the flow?
Strike when the right time comes.
Like a crocodile, Auntie?
That's too boring.
Like they say, Auntie…
you must try and try until--
You die?
Seriously, can you please
just be Julio's pawn for now?
My goodness.
I don't know what I'd do
if something happens to you.
Don't worry, Auntie.
That's really sweet of you.
Thank you for your concern.
But if anyone's going to die here,
it definitely won't be me.
First, it'll be Lily Cruz.
Then, Ivy Aguas, and then…
Let's not mention the last one.
It might just come true.
[sighs]
Relax, Auntie.
[exhales]
THE MONEY'S ALREADY
AT THE PICK-UP POINT.
[laughs]
Oh, here it is.
Looks like I finally got
the money you sent.
[laughs]
Thanks.
Great, you got what you wanted.
Now, give me Ivy.
-Now, now…
-I said give me Ivy!
Shh…
Now…
Take this.
You'll find Ivy Aguas here.
Come on.
Take it.
[unsettling music playing]
Come closer.
Closer!
[unsettling music continues]
I said closer.
Come on, just a little more.
Don't be so shy.
Come on.
You're so close.
Just a little more.
[grunts]
This is for torturing me back then!
And this is for what you
bastards did to my sibling!
[grunts]
This is revenge for all the
innocent lives you've killed!
But, remember this, Mayor.
I'm not alone!
There are plenty more
waiting in line to make you pay.
You're lucky I'm a good man.
And that I didn't kill your fiancée.
[tense music playing]
But you better hurry.
Or you might not reach her alive.
[tense music continues]
You and Ivy Aguas
will be reunited in hell.
[tense music playing]
[unsettling music playing]
Rufo!
How'd you get inside?
I know you met with Julio Ardiente.
What did you two talk about?
Will you sell Jaguar out?
[unsettling music playing]
Rufo.
It's dangerous to work for two demons.
Especially if one is an Ardiente.
Too dangerous, actually.
Why?
Will you rat me out?
Why not?
[scoffs]
Well then…
I guess I have no choice!
[tense music playing]
You know what?
You can work for me.
Together, we'll manage
the Ardientes' gambling dens.
I don't trust traitors like you, Rufo.
[laughs]
We both are.
We aren't, Rufo.
What you want is money.
I want their lives.
[grunts]
Let go!
[action music playing]
[grunts]
Help me!
Help!
Help! Help!
Kill him!
He's one of the Ardientes' men!
-Hurry up!
-Call your boss!
He needs to learn the truth.
-What are you waiting for?!
-Jaguar!
-Come on, help me!
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
[ominous music playing]
[doctor] Julio, I'm sorry…
but your cancer is back.
Bone cancer is very dangerous.
Are you saying my days are numbered?
Julio, we have to conduct more tests.
No!
Neither this disease nor that
bastard Jaguar can kill me!
Now that his right hand
is under my control,
I'll know how to finish him off.
[ominous music playing]
So, when we meet again,
I expect you to bring
Jaguar's head with you.
Of course I will, Julio.
Like you, I also expect
the reward you promised.
You'll give me all of Jaguar's
businesses when he's gone,
and you'll appoint me to the
position you told me about.
[chuckles]
You know, I like ambitious people.
Because they will do everything they can
just to fulfill their dreams.
[ominous music playing]
[groans]
-Jaguar!
-Kill him! Hurry up!
-You need to know the truth.
Jaguar, I caught him.
He's one of the Ardientes' men. Kill him!
Jaguar, you're the biggest
threat to the Ardientes.
Will you let this traitor lie to you?
Don't believe him! He's lying!
You're a liar!
-Give me your gun!
-Jaguar, he's a liar.
I saw him talking to Julio Ardiente.
-Now, you decide.
-[Rufo] Give me your gun!
Give me your gun! Oh, come on!
-You!
-Jaguar.
Give me your gun! Let's kill him!
[Rufo] Give it to me!
What's wrong with you?!
Give me a gun!
Come on! Jaguar…
Jaguar…
Don't.
Please don't, Jaguar.
Don't, Jaguar. Please…
[tense music playing]
-[gunshot]
-[Rufo groaning]
[Rufo groaning]
Jaguar, if I were you, I'd finish him off
before he becomes an asset
to the Ardientes.
[tense music playing]
The boss is asking what reward you want:
money or weapons?
[tense music playing]
I want to be part of your group.
[grunts]
[tense music playing]
[groans]
[chokes]
Stop it! Enough, Jaguar!
Please stop.
Have mercy on me, please.
Do you know what I do
to traitors like you?
I cut them in half.
[sobbing]
Jaguar, no!
[chainsaw starts]
[screams]
No, Jaguar! I'm begging you!
[screaming and sobbing]
Here.
Your boss is looking for you.
This is what I'll do.
I'll send him half of your body.
[sobbing]
-No!
-Listen, all of you!
Don't you even try to copy this bastard!
Don't do what this traitor did.
Do you understand?!
Boss, what about Madrigal?
Can we trust him?
Have mercy, Jaguar!
Ivy?
Ivy!
[suspenseful music playing]
[Arthur] You might not reach her alive.
You and Ivy Aguas
will be reunited in hell.
He lied to me.
-[whimpers]
-Ivy?
-[muffled screams]
Ivy. Wait, wait.
Come on.
-[muffled crying]
-It's okay. I'm here.
[sobbing]
Don't cry, I'm here.
[sobbing continues]
Don't cry. It's okay.
I'm here. I'm here. I'm here.
It's okay. Calm down.
[sobbing]
Don't cry. It's okay.
It's okay now.
That bastard, what did he do to you?
[sobbing]
[tense music playing]
I'm here. I'm here.
[sobbing]
You're safe now. You're safe now.
-No.
-You're safe now. I'm here.
Ivy, I'm here.
It's Arnaldo.
I'm here. They're gone.
It's just me here. It's okay now.
I'm here. Don't worry.
Hon, who was that?
Why did he kidnap me?
I'm sorry.
Forgive me. This is all my fault.
-Forgive me.
-Our engagement ring…
-He took it!
-It's with me! It's here!
No, it's with him!
It's here! It's here!
I have it! I have it.
-[sobbing]
-I have it.
It's all right.
Stop crying. We're safe now.
He said I should be careful around you.
He said I shouldn't go near you.
Why? What did you do to him?
What did you do, hon?
[Arnaldo] I can easily
kill you if I wanted to.
And I can make it look like
you committed suicide
just like what I did to Carlotta.
Or I can also pin the blame
on someone else,
just like I framed Diego
when I killed Nimfa.
I… I don't know. I don't remember.
I can't even recall his face.
All I know is that he's crazy.
But don't be scared.
Don't think about that, okay?
Don't believe him, okay?
I won't do anything bad to you.
[stammers] I will never hurt you.
Okay? I'm here. You're safe now.
Okay?
Stop crying. Stop crying. Stop crying.
No one can hurt you anymore.
I won't let anything happen to you again.
-[sniffles]
-Okay?
Stop crying.
Let's go home. Let's go home.
I'll have a doctor see you too.
Okay?
Let's go home.
Let's go.
Can you stand?
Slowly. Slowly.
[suspenseful music playing]
-Hon, is he really gone?
-He's gone.
What if he's still here?
[suspenseful music playing]
Papa.
So, your informant's not responding, eh?
Maybe Jaguar has already intercepted him.
You know, I really have
a strong feeling, Papa.
He's really watching us.
Shut up, Emilia!
Keep your trap shut
before I take all my anger
at Jaguar out on you!
That's not fair at all, Papa!
You're too harsh!
You're such a sore loser.
Don't worry, Papa.
We can still get our revenge
on that Jaguar.
For your information, I am not a loser.
Yeah, Papa, but the score still stands.
Jaguar, one.
Julio, zero.
Is that your new job?
Are you a sports statistician now?
You're keeping scores on us?
[scoffs]
I can see it! You're smirking!
You want to laugh at me
because I'm losing.
Are you glad that I'm losing?!
-Hmm?
-Is that the case?
[tense music playing]
I will prove to you that the person
who can defeat Julio Ardiente
is yet to be born.
[suspenseful music playing]
[line rings]
It's me.
I want you to do me a favor.
I want you to mount a manhunt
against this hoodlum Jaguar.
I want you to find him, catch him…
and kill him.
ASAP.
Yes, please. Do me that favor.
I want you to end his life.
Now…
Let's see what that Jaguar
will do once he learns
that the police aren't
the only ones after him…
but a whole private army.
Papa, you really are mad.
I'm not just mad.
My blood is curdling from fury.
And I promise you, I will make
that Jaguar lose his manhood.
[tense music playing]
This is from the boss.
[ominous music playing]
[phone rings]
[ringing continues]
-Boss.
-Welcome to my group.
From now on, that will be your uniform.
But there's one thing I'll ask of you.
[distorted voice] I hope you can do it.
I just want you to be loyal to me.
And you'll get everything you want.
I hear you loud and clear, boss.
Very good.
Wait for my next call.
I have a task for you.
[suspenseful music playing]
[somber music playing]
Hon?
You can't look this way, okay?
We need to fix you up.
Appear as if nothing happened.
I don't want Grandpa to see you like this,
because the election stress
is taking a toll on him,
and I don't want to add to that.
Is that okay?
Can we pretend as if nothing happened?
Can we do that? I'm sorry
if I'm asking too much.
It's okay, hon.
Okay.
[somber music playing]
What?
Thank you.
[sobbing]
[sniffles] Thanks, hon.
Thank you.
Thank you for saving me.
When I was locked up,
while I was locked up, hon,
when he was hurting me,
when he told me that
he was going to kill me,
I was so scared!
I was so scared that I'd die,
that we'd never get married.
That I'd never be with you anymore.
So, thank you, hon.
Thank you for saving me.
I'm sorry it took longer.
[sniffles]
I'm sorry I took too long.
When you were gone,
I didn't know what to do.
I couldn't imagine a life without you.
Hon.
I don't think I could take it.
What if we get married right away?
Let's get married soon-- Sooner.
I want to marry you sooner.
-Yes.
-I want to prove to everyone
that they can't go against our love.
They can't break what we have.
-Let's get married sooner.
-Yes.
Next week.
Yes.
Yes, hon.
Yes, please.
[tense music playing]
I won't let anyone hurt you.
Prepare the guest room, hurry.
Arnaldo? What happened?
Grandpa, I think she got food poisoning
from the restaurant where we had our date.
Are you sure?
Yeah. I'm sure.
The doctor's on his way. We'll go now.
[unsettling music playing]
Anna…
I can't calm down until
I speak to my daughter.
What if Ivy's with Jepoy?
Do you know anything about Lily's plan?
No, but Jepoy told me
he's going to find a way
to stop Ivy and Arnaldo's wedding.
There's Jepoy.
Jepoy, where have you been?
Observing the Ardientes. Why?
-Jepoy…
-Ma'am?
Did you see Lily there?
She wasn't there.
Did something happen to her?
[ominous music playing]
Other than early signs
of dehydration and fatigue,
your fiancée is okay.
Thanks, doc.
Um, doc?
Can you please check
my daughter-in-law thoroughly?
She might be suffering from
"overacting syndrome"
or "dramatictitis." Don't you think?
[Arnaldo] Mom!
[doctor] Excuse me.
I'm just concerned.
You don't look concerned.
You're no stranger to
plotting against Ivy's life.
Did you have anything to do with this?
Hey! You, young man,
don't talk to me that way.
How dare you?
Don't pin this on me.
I had nothing to do with this.
Then why are you--
Oh, shut up!
-[exhales]
-[Arnaldo] Sorry.
Sorry.
[unsettling music playing]
You must forgive your mother.
She has this weird spell,
especially when there's a full moon out.
[chuckles]
Anyway, you two rest. Okay?
Grandpa?
Before you leave,
Ivy and I want to tell you something.
What is it?
Well, we want to…
we want our wedding to happen soon.
How soon?
Next week.
Next week…
We can make that happen.
Next week will be good.
I'm okay with that.
Truth of the matter is,
I can't wait to see you get married.
-Wonderful.
-Thank you.
Thank you, Congressman.
You're very welcome, Miss Aguas.
And don't worry.
I will make sure that nothing
will get in the way of your wedding.
Now get some rest.
Thank you, Grandpa.
[ominous music playing]
We have been preparing for the forthcoming
Aguas-Ardiente royal wedding.
It is finally going to happen
a week from today.
No! No! No! No!
[Arnaldo] You think
I don't know what you did?
You had Arthur kidnap Ivy.
You can't stop our wedding!
I'll put a stop to all your plans.
No!
[Jepoy] Now that I have money and weapons,
I will stop your wedding
with bullets, Arnaldo.
[theme music playing]